PROFILE

Hello, my name is Dustin. I'm a Front-End Developer living in Toronto. I have experience building responsive, accessible websites and web applications. I spent the past 10 years managing and running Magento and Shopify based e-commerce websites. In that time I improved user experience and worked closely with devs to implement new features and solve bugs.

PROJECTS

Gif The News

React | JavaScript | APIs

Live Link

Memory Card Matching Game
JavaScript | jQuery | Sass
Live Link

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Ecommerce Specialist at A.J. Sports World, Toronto

JULY 2019 — FEBRUARY 2020

- Improved category landing page design using HTML and CSS to boost clickthrough rate by 10%
- Maintained product data across multiple sales channels using excel to keep track of ever changing pricing and product details.
- Created a more efficient workflow for product updates using custom Excel templates.

Director of e-Commerce at 1800wheelchair.com, New York City

MAY 2011 — APRIL 2019

- Orchestrated monthly A/B design testing and execution, measuring and reporting all results.
- Directed the development team to effectively resolve bugs and implement requested changes and features.
- Ensured user-experience was informative, easy to navigate and interactive.

Owner at The Bowling Universe

JANUARY 2016 — MAY 2020

- Created a bowling brand and Shopify site, growing traffic organically from zero to 25k monthly users.
- Created and commissioned content based on keyword research to successfully rank for multiple keywords in the SERPs at the zero and first position.
- Organically grew an Instagram following of 4k+ followers in the first 5 months.

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology, Front End Web Development
Guilford Technical Community College, Computer Information Technology

dk@dustinkelly.dev

416-688-3346 679 Euclid Ave Toronto, Canada

LINKS

Dustinkelly.dev LinkedIn

SKILLS

JavaScript

React

jQuery

HTML5

CSS3

Sass

Frontend

Development

Firebase

GitHub

Responsive Design

User Experience

e-Commerce Site Administration